A Guide to the Diplomas Collection
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- McCue, W. T. 1873 (Box 3)
  Elmington Military and Classical, Diploma, Arithmetic
- McCue, W. T. 1873 (Box 3)
  Elmington Military and Classical, Diploma, Latin
- McGrath, Thomas 1899 (Box 3)
- McGuire, Joseph A. 1899 (Box 3)
- McGuire, Joseph A. 1899 (Box 3)
- McGuire, Joseph A. 1899 (Box 3)
- McIlwaine, William B. 1915 (Box 3)
- McIlwaine, William B. 1915 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Economics and Political Science
- McIlwaine, William B. 1907 (Box 3)
- McNagny, Philips McC. 1907 (Box 3)
- McNagny, Philips McC. 1906 (Box 3)
- McNeill, James A. 1868 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Constitutional and International Law
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1860 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1860 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Greek
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1860 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Mathematics
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1860 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1860 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1858 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1858 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1858 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1858 (Box 3)
- Meriwether, Francis T. 1857 (Box 3)
- Merz, Albert Ronald 1910 (Box 3)
- Merz, Albert Ronald 1910 (Box 3)
- Merz, Albert Ronald 1909 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Botany
- Merz, Albert Ronald 1906 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Industrial Chemistry
- Midgette, D. R., Jr. 1911 (Box 3)
- Midgette, D. R., Jr. 1911 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Political Economy
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1868 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1867 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1867 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1867 (Box 3)
- Miller, Alamby M. 1866 (Box 3)
- Miller, Guy. 1888 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, Medicine
- Miller, Robert W. 1899 (Box 3)
- Minnigerode, George T. 1900 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, B.A., English Literature
- Minor, John 1915 (Box 3)
- Minor, Nannie 1887 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Algebra
- Minor, Nannie 1887 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Arithmetic
- Minor, Nannie 1887 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Latin
- Minor, Nannie 1887 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Drawing
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Botany
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Roman History
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Greek History
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Mythology
- Minor, Nannie 1886 (Box 3)
  Edgehill School for Girls, Diploma, Philosophy
- Moomaw, John C. 1906 (Box 3)
- Moomaw, John C. 1904 (Box 3)
- Moon, Basil G. 1900 (Box 3)
- Moore, Andrew S. 1899 (Box 3)
- Moore, William C. 1900 (Box 3)
- Moore, William C. 1900 (Box 3)
- Nalle, Brodie C. 1900 (Box 3)
- Nalle, Brodie C. 1900 (Box 3)
- Nelson, Alexander C. 1899 (Box 3)
- Nelson, Alexander H. 1913 (Box 3)
- Nelson, George S. 1902 (Box 3)
- Nelson, Thomas K. 1901 (Box 3)
- Nelson, Thomas K. 1901 (Box 3)
- Newcomb, John L. 1902 (Box 3)
- Newman, Carol M. 1901 (Box 3)
- Nininger, Sigourney F. 1904 (Box 3)
- Nolting, Frederick Ernest 1940 (Box 3)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Philosophy
- Norfleet, Paul J. 1899 (Box 3)
- Norwood, Annie J. 1980 (Box 3)
  Danville College for Young Ladies, Graduate, French
- Osborne, Julian 1904 (Box 3)
  niversity of Virginia, Graduate, English Literature
- Owen, Leartus J. 1899 (Box 3)
- Painter, Landon C. 1913 (Box 4)
- Parkhill, John H., 1842 (Box 4)
- Parkins, John H. 1905 (Box 4)
- Parkins, John H. 1905 (Box 4)
- Parrish, G. Hinston 1895 (Box 4)
- Parrish, Robert L. 1899 (Box 4)
- Parsons, Charles H. 1913 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1888 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1888 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, Latin
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, High School
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, German
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, Trigonometry
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, Geometry
- Perry, J. Martin 1887 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, Greek
- Perry, J. Martin 1886 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1886 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1886 (Box 4)
- Perry, J. Martin 1886 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, Algebra
- Perry, J. Martin 1886 (Box 4)
  Shenandoah Valley Academy (Winchester, Va.), Diploma, English
- Persinger, David W. 1900 (Box 4)
- Persinger, David W. 1900 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Graduate, Moral Philosophy (Logic and Psychology)
- Petty, C. L. 1915 (Box 4)
- Peyton, George W. 1902 (Box 4)
- Pierce, S. Blackwell 1895 (Box 4)
- Pierce, S. Blackwell 1895 (Box 4)
- Pillow, James H. 1900 (Box 4)
- Pillow, James H. 1900 (Box 4)
- Pillow, James H. 1900 (Box 4)
- Pillow, James H. 1900 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, CHemistry
- Pitzer, Mary M. 1917 (Box 4)
  Maury High School (Norfolk, Va.), Diploma
- Poats, Thomas G. 1906 (Box 4)
- Porter, A. W. 1915 (Box 4)
- Porter, Joseph Y., Jr. 1900 (Box 4)
- Powel, John 1908 (Box 4)
  Société Astronomique de France, Certificate
- Powell, John H. 1858 (Box 4)
- Powell, John H. 1858 (Box 4)
- Powell, John H. 1855 (Box 4)
- Powers, Sidney E. 1915 (Box 4)
- Pratt, John L. 1905 (Box 4)
- Preston, John M., Jr. 1860 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Proficiency, Moral Philosophy
- Price, Overton M. 1895 (Box 4)
- Prichard, Robert S. 1870 (Box 4)
- Radford, William M. 1830 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Philsophy
- Rahim, Abur 1966 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, M.S., Civil Engineering
- Ramsay, George D. 1895 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Obstetrics and Gynecology
- Ramsay, George D. 1895 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Arthur G. 1895 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1905 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, J.D., Law
- Randolph, Harrison 1894 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Latin
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, B.A., French
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, B.A., German
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Mathematics (Pure)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1892 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1891 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1891 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Logic
- Randolph, Harrison 1890 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1890 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1890 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1889 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Harrison 1889 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Oscar de W. 1907 (Box 4)
- Randolph, Oscar de W. 1907 (Box 4)
- Reed, Frank W. 1906 (Box 4)
- Reed, Pembroke W. 1900 (Box 4)
- Renshaw, W. C. Wickham 1902 (Box 4)
- Renshaw, W. C. Wickham 1902 (Box 4)
- Renshaw, W. C. Wickham 1902 (Box 4)
- Rhett, Andrew B. 1907 (Box 4)
- Rhodes, Roscoe B. 1906 (Box 4)
- Richardson, Ambrose M. 1901 (Box 4)
- Richardson, Hilary G. 1895 (Box 4)
- Riely, Henry C. 1895 (Box 4)
- Riely, Henry C. 1895 (Box 4)
- Riely, Henry C. 1895 (Box 4)
- Rind, Robert C. 1895 (Box 4)
- Ritchie, William F. 1830 (Box 4)
- Rives, William C. 1847 (Box 4)
  Harvard University, B.L., Law
- Rives, William C. 1844 (Box 4)
- Rives, William C. 1844 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Italian Language and Literature
- Rives, William C. 1844 (Box 4)
- Rives, William C. 1844 (Box 4)
- Rives, William C. 1843 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Ancient Languages and Literature
- Rives, William C. 1843 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1841 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1840 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1840 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1840 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1839 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Spanish Language
- Rives, Francis R. 1839 (Box 4)
- Rives, Francis R. 1839 (Box 4)
- Roberts, Floyd H. 1900 (Box 4)
- Robertson, J. H. 1915 (Box 4)
- Robertson, Walter H. 1900 (Box 4)
- Rogers, Alexander H. 1841 (Box 4)
  University of Pennsylvania, M.D., Medicine
- Rogers, Alexander H. 1840 (Box 4)
- Rowe, Joseph E. 1905 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1924 (Box 4)
  Phi Beta Pi, University of Virginia, Certificate
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1907 (Box 4)
  Masonic Home of Virginia, Certificate
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1899 (Box 4)
  Virginia State Board of Medical Examiners, Certificate, Medicine
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1899 (Box 4)
  State Board of Medical Examiners, Certificate, Medicine
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1898 (Box 4)
  New York Infant Asylum, Certificate
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1897 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1896 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1896 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Pathology and Hygiene
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1896 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1896 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1891 (Box 4)
  Norfolk Academy (Norfolk, Va.), Diploma
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1890 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1889 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1888 (Box 4)
- Royster, Lawrence T. 1887 (Box 4)
- Royster, William S. 1900 (Box 4)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Chemistry (Agricultural)
- Sabine, Percy T. 1915 (Box 5)
- Saegmuller, Frederick B. 1902 (Box 5)
- Sandridge, J. D. 1915 (Box 5)
- Sawyer, J. G. 1909 (Box 5)
- Scott, John W. 1879 (Box 5)
- Scott, John W. 1878 (Box 5)
- Scott, John W. 1878 (Box 5)
- Scott, John W. 1877 (Box 5)
- Scott, John W. 1877 (Box 5)
- Scott, Robert D. 1915 (Box 5)
- Searcy, Walter R. 1890 (Box 5)
- Sears, Otis B. 1901 (Box 5)
- Seyfert, William Hunter, III 1966 (Box 5)
- Shackleford, Grigsby C. 1905 (Box 5)
- Shackleford, Grigsby C. 1905 (Box 5)
- Shaffer, Elmer M. 1899 (Box 5)
- Sharp, Tilghman H. 1915 (Box 5)
- Shelton, Carroll J. 1911 (Box 5)
- Simms, Lyman Moody, Jr. 1966 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Ph.D., History
- Sims, William B., Jr. 1915 (Box 5)
- Smith, Edward N. 1915 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Biblical History and Literature
- Smith, Francis H. 1850 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Chemistry
- Smith, Gessner H. 1886 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1882 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1881 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1881 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1880 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1879 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1879 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1879 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1878 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1878 (Box 5)
- Smith, Gessner H. 1878 (Box 5)
- Smith, H. B. 1909 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1897 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Physics
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, M.A., English Literature
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1896 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, B.A., Physics
- Smith, James D. 1895 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1895 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1894 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1894 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1894 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Geometry
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, High School
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, United States History and Composition
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Deportment
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Latin
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, French
- Smith, James D. 1891 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Algebra and Trigonometry
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Penmanship and Orthography
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Algebra
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, English grammar and composition
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Arithmetic
- Smith, James D. 1890 (Box 5)
  Greenwood School (Albemarle County, Va.), Diploma, Geography
- Smith, Sommerfield 1858 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1858 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1858 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1857 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1857 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1857 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1857 (Box 5)
- Smith, Sommerfield 1856 (Box 5)
- Smythe, Langdon C. McC. 1905 (Box 5)
- Smythe, Langdon C. McC. 1905 (Box 5)
- Smythe, Langdon C. McC. 1905 (Box 5)
- Smythe, Langdon C. McC. 1904 (Box 5)
- Snoddy, Elmer E. 1934 (Box 5)
  Transylvania University, D.D., Religion
- Snoddy, Elmer E. 1928 (Box 5)
  Drake University, J.D., Law
- Snoddy, Elmer E. 1910 (Box 5)
  Yale University, M.A.
- Snoddy, Elmer E. 1898 (Box 5)
  Hiram College, M.A., Religion
- Snoddy, Elmer E. 1896 (Box 5)
  Hiram College, B.A.
- Snoddy, Leland B. 1929 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Ph.D., Physics
- Snoddy, Leland B. 1923 (Box 5)
  University of Kentucky, M.A.
- Snoddy, Leland B. 1921 (Box 5)
  University of Kentucky, B.S., Chemistry (Industrial)
- Snoddy, Virginia C. 1925 (Box 5)
  University of California, Berkeley, M.A., Household Science
- Somers, G. T. 1909 (Box 5)
- Stacy, George P. 1899 (Box 5)
- Stallinger, Robert E. 1901 (Box 5)
- Stead, William F. 1908 (Box 5)
- Stevens, Arthur K. 1905 (Box 5)
- Stirewalt, William J. 1905 (Box 5)
- Stirewalt, William J. 1904 (Box 5)
- Stratton, Leonard L. 1915 (Box 5)
- Strode, Aubrey E. 1899 (Box 5)
- Stuart, Henry C., Jr. 1913 (Box 5)
- Stuart, Henry C., Jr. 1913 (Box 5)
- Stuart, Henry C., Jr. 1913 (Box 5)
- Stuart, Warren H. 1900 (Box 5)
- Stuart, Warren H. 1900 (Box 5)
- Swift, Herman H. 1900 (Box 5)
- Swift, Herman H. 1900 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1870 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, B.Lit., Bachelor of Letters
- Taylor, Charles E. 1870 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1870 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1869 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1868 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1867 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Literature
- Taylor, Charles E. 1867 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1866 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1866 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Charles E. 1866 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Rawleigh W.D. 1905 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Language (Italian)
- Taylor, Rawleigh W.D. 1904 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Rawleigh W.D. 1904 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1887 (Box 7)
  University of Virginia, B.Phil.
- Taylor, Robert C. 1886 (Box 7)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1884 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1884 (Box 7)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 7)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, English Language and Literature
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, B.Lit.
- Taylor, Robert C. 1883 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1882 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1882 (Box 5)
- Taylor, Robert C. 1882 (Box 5)
- Tebbs, Willoughby W. 1857 (Box 5)
- Tebbs, Willoughby W. 1848 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Anglo Saxon Language and Literature
- Tebbs, Willoughby W. 1848 (Box 5)
- Tebbs, Willoughby W. 1848 (Box 5)
- Towles, Oliver P. 1906 (Box 5)
- Towles, William B. 1896 (Box 5)
- Towles, William B. 1893 (Box 5)
  University of Vermont, Certificate of Proficiency
- Towles, William B. 1868 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Anatomy
- Towles, William B. 1868 (Box 5)
  University of Virginia, Certificate of Proficiency, Physiology
- Trummell, Miles F. 1915 (Box 5)
- Tucker, Ellis N. 1915 (Box 5)
- Tucker, Ellis N. 1913 (Box 5)
- Tucker, F. Bland 1913 (Box 5)
- Tunger, Henry J. 1913 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, Joseph A. 1860 (Box 5)
- Turner, David Burnham 1966 (Box 5)
- Upshur, R. L. 1915 (Box 6)
- Voight, Gilbert P. 1913 (Box 6)
- Walker, James F. 1915 (Box 6)
- Walker, James T. 1904 (Box 6)
- Walker, James T. 1904 (Box 6)
- Walker, John S. 1902 (Box 6)
- Walker, John S. 1901 (Box 6)
- Walker, John S. 1901 (Box 6)
- Walker, Ripley S. 1913 (Box 6)
- Walter, Garrett 1902 (Box 6)
- Watson, Price M. 1837 (Box 6)
- Wayland, John W. 1907 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, Ph.D., Philosophy
- Weakley, Charles E., Jr. 1906 (Box 6)
- Weakley, Charles E., Jr. 1906 (Box 6)
- Webb, Robert H. 1904 (Box 6)
- Wenn, Francis A. 1905 (Box 6)
- Wertenbaker, Thomas J. 1907 (Box 6)
- Wertenbaker, Thomas J. 1902 (Box 6)
- Wertenbaker, Thomas J. 1900 (Box 6)
- White, James L. 1915 (Box 6)
- White, L. Matthews 1902 (Box 6)
- White, L. Matthews 1902 (Box 6)
- White, Robb, Jr. 1901 (Box 6)
- Whitmore, Harry G. 1907 (Box 6)
- Whitmore, Harry G. 1906 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Geology
- Whitmore, Harry G. 1901 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, M.A., Chemistry (Analytical)
- Williams, Charles U. 1899 (Box 6)
- Williams, Howard H. 1895 (Box 6)
- Williams, William G. 1895 (Box 6)
- Williams, R. Gray 1899 (Box 6)
- Williamson, Rush H. 1899 (Box 6)
- Wilson, James S. 1905 (Box 6)
- Wilson, L. T. 1911 (Box 6)
- Wilson, Gordon 1899 (Box 6)
- Wilson, Harry L. 1901 (Box 6)
- Wilson, Fred R. 1923 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, B.S., Chemical Engineering
- Wilson, Fred R. 1919 (Box 6)
  Diploma, High School
- Woods, Samuel B., Jr. 1906 (Box 6)
- Woods, Samuel B., Jr. 1905 (Box 6)
- Woods, Samuel B., Jr. 1904 (Box 6)
- Worthington, Hugh S. 1902 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Romance Langauges
- Worthington, Hugh S. 1902 (Box 6)
- Worthington, Hugh S. 1902 (Box 6)
- Wright, Charles C. 1915 (Box 6)
- Wright, Joseph 1895 (Box 6)
- Wright, Joseph 1895 (Box 6)
  University of Virginia, Graduate, Mechanics
- Yancy, Edward B. 1908 (Box 6)
- Yancy, Edward B. 1908 (Box 6)
- Yancy, Philo B. 1906 (Box 6)
- Yates, Edward S. 1895 (Box 6)